James Ciclitira

Product Designer based in London, creating complex digital products that lead to better user experiences. I love to design beautifully simple interfaces, code, iterate and create. I am an experienced and capable Digital Product Designer with over two years' professional experience.

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

CrowdScores · September 2015 - January 2017

CrowdScores is a real-time sports data application. I had the pleasure of working as the principal designer, taking responsibility for a variety of roles. Responsibilities included improving the existing product, researching and developing new features, conceptualising ideas and prototyping.

Product & Web Development

Suggestv · January 2017 - April 2017

Suggestv is the inventor of semantic video distribution. I was responsible for designing and facilitating the production of a semantic video distribution platform using React.

Freelance Designer

Numilli · January 2017 - Present

Numilli - Bitcoin safe and easy. Numilli aims to makes it easy to securely buy and sell bitcoin currency on the go using a mobile app and ATM machine. My ongoing responsibility is the design and branding for the mobile app, web platform and ATM machines

EDUCATION

The University of Edinburgh · 2011 - 2015 Product design - 2:1 BA (Hons)

DESIGN SKILLS

Sketching
UI/UX Design
Interaction Design
Prototyping
Grid & Layout
Design Research

DESIGN TOOLS













DEVELOPMENT





